Coming here to die? What idiots.
居然自己跑来送死 真是笨啊
Fighting with you is boring.
太无聊了吧
Come together.
干脆全都一起上吧
I don't even know which is the magic beast.
到底谁才是魔兽啊？
Song is as strong as a monster too.
老宋也是强得跟怪物一样啊
It's about done here.
这里解决得差不多了
Sung, you've really gotten stronger.
不过阿成 你真的变强了
Where did you get that great dagger?
你是从哪儿弄到那么好的短剑？
Jinwoo, I haven't had a chance to heal you today.
这么说起来 振宇
I hope you won't need it this time.
希望这次任务全程都轮不到我出场
No, I'm counting on you.
别这么说 就靠你了
Just as I thought.
果然没错 他真的变了很多
Not just his appearance, but even his aura.
不只是外表 连气场都变了
I can feel his ease and confidence.
甚至感觉这里对他来说是游刃有余
Did you learn martial arts?
你是有去学什么格斗技吗？
Let's keep going.
继续前进吧
It's a fork in the road.
是岔路
This one is even easier than expected.
这里的难度比想象中还低
Should we split up into three groups?
要不要兵分三路行动？
Although it will increase the risk,
虽然会提升一些风险
we could end the mission sooner.
但就可以早点结束这个任务
Let's do that.
就这么做吧
I'll take the right path with those convicts.
我带那些受刑人走右边那条路
If you find the boss room,
要是发现了头目房 请马上过来通知我
It must be because my perception has improved.
是感知能力提升的关系吧
From here, I can tell…
从这里也能感觉到
The boss is ahead on this path.
头目就在这条路的前方
I can't earn many points from fighting goblins.
只是打哥布林是赚不了多少经验值的
Mr. Song.
宋大叔
Let's take the left path.
我们走左边那条路吧
I got it.
好
Yes.
好的
I can handle goblins of this level.
这种程度的哥布林我还能对付
It should.
应该可以吧
They brought the weakest hunter, so the level of this dungeon must be low.
都找最弱兵器来了 表示这个地下城等级很低
We thought so too last time, didn't we?
我们之前也是因为那样 而掉以轻心吧？
I've decided.
我决定了
Once this mission is over,
等这次的突击任务结束
I will go apologize to Sung.
-我也要去向阿成低头道歉 -什么？
You couldn't forget it either, right?
你心里也一直有疙瘩吧？
We ran away.
我们逃跑了
A man who prides himself as a hunter ran away.
堂堂一个以猎人为职的大人居然逃跑
I did it for my family,
虽说是为了家人
but it doesn't change the fact that I abandoned my companion.
但是抛弃同伴
If we want to continue claiming to be hunters,
如果今后还想以猎人自称的话
we must learn to admit our mistakes.
就必须要先学会承认错误
Will he forgive us?
我们能得到他的原谅吗？
He will never forgive us.
不可能吧
But I still have to apologize.
即便如此 我还是要去道歉
All right, let's go.
好了 我们快走吧
Too weak.
太弱了吧
Goblins are no match at all.
打哥布林完全不过瘾嘛
Finished them all?
全都收拾掉了吗？
It's a piece of cake.
我能秒杀这种怪物
I'm not even satisfied.
我还杀得不够满足呢
What if they were humans?
如果它们是人的话呢？
Can you do the same?
你们也一样下得了手吗？
Humans aren't that different from these magic beasts.
人类跟这些魔兽差不了多少吧
Yeah, they're all the same.
是啊 都一样啦
What do you want from me?
你要找我谈什么？
Three men violated my daughter.
有三个男的侵犯了我的女儿
She hanged herself.
后来我的女儿上吊自杀
My wife ended up in a mental hospital due to the trauma.
我老婆也因为精神受创而住进医院
But those three guys
但是那三个混蛋
will be released in a few years as if nothing had happened.
却只要被关个几年 就能像没事一般被放出来
And they…
而且那些家伙居然还持有猎人资格
I've heard that hunters can get sentence reductions
听说猎人就算是在服刑中 只要参加突击任务就能获得减刑
It's not fair at all!
怎么会有如此不讲理的事？
My daughter will never return to me.
我的女儿已经无法回到我身边了！
What is that?
那是什么？
Here's three billion.
这里有三十亿
Please…
拜托…
Kill them for me.
请你帮我杀了他们
No outsider would know what happened in the dungeon, right?
地下城里发生的事 外界的人是不会知道的对吧？
I beg you.
求你帮我这个忙！
After leaving here, I'll report to the Surveillance Team
离开这里后 我会跟监察科报告说
that the three of you
你们在这里遇上一百只哥布林
This path is really winding.
这条路弯弯曲曲的耶
Are we really going forward?
我们真的有在前进吗？
Did we choose the wrong path?
难道我们选的是错的路？
Help…
救命啊
Don't expect a quick death.
别以为你能痛快地解脱
I'll torture you as much as possible before ending your lives.
要尽可能折磨 再结束你们的生命
That's what I was told to do.
人家是这么交待的
What… what are you doing?
你在做什么？
That saves me the time to find it.
多亏你们 省得我还要找路
Help me--
救救我…
Although this went differently than planned…
虽然计划产生了些变化…
That Kang Taeshik.
刚刚那个叫姜泰植的人
He and his superior from the Surveillance Team visited me at the hospital.
他曾跟监察科的上司一起来过医院
I hope he doesn't remember me.
希望他不记得我
-Mr. Song. -Okay.
-宋大叔！ -好！
What happened?
这是怎么回事？
Jungho.
正浩！
Joohee… treat them.
珠熙 帮忙治疗
Go treat them!
快帮他们治疗！
Yes!
好的！
Mr. Kim, pull yourself together.
金先生 你振作一点啊
These wounds were not caused by magic beasts.
这些伤不是魔兽造成的
They are caused by sharp blades.
是锐利刀具造成的伤口
Moreover, the enemy avoided lethal injuries to create more wounds.
而且还刻意避开了致命伤 砍了好几刀
It's no use.
没用的
I can't survive.
反正我已经没救了
What nonsense is that?
你在胡说什么？
You need to be alive.
你要好好活下去啊
Don't you have a family?
你不是还有家人吗？
You must…
你要是…
You must live no matter what!
要是不拼命活到最后一刻
Only then can I hate you.
我不就没办法恨你了吗？
I'm sorry.
对不起
I am truly sorry.
真的很抱歉
I didn't want to apologize like this.
我本来不是想用这种方式来向你道歉
I wanted to bow my head and apologize to you.
我原本想郑重地向你低头谢罪
Sung.
小哥
I am really sorry.
我真的对不起你
Believe me.
这是我的真心话
Kim.
老金
You're quite agile.
挺快的嘛
I wanted to take care of the healer first.
本来是想先解决治疗师的
I didn't expect that move to be blocked.
想不到刚刚那招居然会被挡下来
Mr. Kang.
姜先生！
Did you do this?
这些是你做的吗？
What if I did?
是又怎样？
Aren't you from the Hunter's Association?
你不是猎人协会的人吗？
How could you do this--
怎么能做出这种事？
I've thought of a good story.
我想到一个好剧本了
I was going to claim that you were killed by goblins
我本来是想对外宣称 你们全被哥布林歼灭
but I want to make a change.
但我要修改一下方向
These criminals attempted to escape.
这些企图逃跑的罪犯先动手杀了你们
and ambushed me from behind when I fought the boss.
后来又趁我忙着对付头目时
However, with their strength, they couldn't harm me.
然而凭他们的实力根本赢不了我
In the end, only I survived.
所以最后只有我一个人活了下来
Perfect, isn't it?
怎么样？很完美吧？
You can't defeat him.
你是打不赢他的
Let me do it.
让我来吧
Kim, lend me your sword.
老金 借我一用
It's been a long time since I've crossed swords with someone.
我已经很久没对人刀剑相向了
He is B-rank, higher than me.
对手是B级 等级比我高
But…
但是…
Joohee, can you cast a physical enhancement spell on me?
珠熙 可以在我身上施加 肉体强化魔法吗？
Y-Yes.
好的
Assassins usually have low defense, and that's their weakness.
暗杀系通常都会有防御力不高的缺点
Even if an old mage had his strength enhanced,
一个年老法师即使增强了力量
it would only backfire.
也只会有反效果而已
Right now, I am a swordsman.
现在的我是个剑士
You are a mage.
毕竟只是个法师型猎人
What's the point of picking up a sword?
拿起了剑又有什么意义？
There might be a point.
也可能是有意义的
You have good skills.
身手还不错
Although enhanced, your movements are very skilled in themselves.
虽说有增益效果加持
Although just for a moment, Mr. Song caught up to his speed.
虽然只有一瞬间 但宋大叔追上了他的速度
If he could be a bit faster…
要是能再快一点的话…
Your attack is fast and accurate.
攻势又快又准
You have the ability to attack with a sword instead of magic.
确实是有能够放弃魔法 拿剑攻击的实力
But that's all there is to it.
不过也就只有那点程度而已
That healer is annoying.
那个治疗师真是碍事
I should get rid of you first.
果然还是要先解决你
Turning your back on a swordsman?
你居然背对拿着剑的对手
After all, I am the master of an S-rank hunter.
好歹我也是个S级猎人的师父
In terms of swordsmanship, I won't lose to you.
要比剑术的话 我不会输你的
That being said,
话虽如此
the power you've been granted is ultimately limited.
但你被赋予的力量终究有限
A mage
区区一个法师
can never keep up with an assassin.
是不可能跟得上暗杀系猎人的速度的
Mr. Song.
宋大叔！
No.
不会吧
The healer has exhausted her power.
看来治疗师的力量也用尽了
It's over.
结束了
Did it work?
奏效了吗？
You posed as a swordsman to lower my guard against the magic.
坚持当个剑士 好降低我对魔法的戒心
You unleashed a magical attack just before I was going to make my final strike.
看准我使出最后一击的前一刻 发动魔法攻击
The tactic wasn't bad.
这个战术还不赖
You cunning old fox.
你这只老狐狸
Is it over?
到此为止了吗？
Die.
去死吧
You again.
又是你？
Who are you?
你到底是什么人？
I'm Sung Jinwoo,
成振宇
an E-rank hunter.
E级猎人
E-rank?
E级？
How is that possible?
这怎么可能
Sung.
阿成 刚刚那到底是怎么回事？
If you are a power-type E-rank hunter,
如果是E级的力量型猎人
that strength would make sense.
的确可能会有刚刚的那种力量
But you reacted fast enough to block my attacks twice.
但你的反应快到能挡下两次我的攻击
Are you an assassin-type?
难道你是暗杀系的吗？
Never mind. It doesn't matter.
算了 你是哪一种也不是很重要
You've been hiding your true power, right?
你还藏了一手？
You seem to know each other.
你们几个看起来彼此认识
Then you can't be a False Ranker.
那你就不可能会是非法登录者
After all, you wouldn't leave any witnesses alive.
因为你不可能会留目击者活口
In that case, there's only one answer.
这样的话 答案只有一个
You're a second awakener.
你是二次觉醒者
Sung is…
阿成是…
A second awakener?
二次觉醒者？
If that's the case, did it happen after the double dungeon incident?
这么说的话
Double dungeon?
“双重地下城”？
Is he… that lousy E-rank hunter?
难不成他是当时的那个E级废物？
His appearance and impression are completely different.
从外表跟气场来看 根本不是同一个人啊
And his measured value was only ten.
而且当时的测定值我记得只有10
Did the second awakening happen after that?
所以是在那之后才觉醒的吗？
If so, how did he survive the double dungeon?
若是如此 他又是如何 从双重地下城里活下来的？
Well, regardless,
算了 无论如何
it seems you have little experience as a hunter.
以猎人来说 你似乎没什么经验
Let me teach you a thing or two.
就让我这个前辈来教你几招吧
Why do you do this?
你为什么要做这种事？
I was entrusted by the family of the victim.
我是受被害人的家属所托
They basically killed someone without any remorse.
他们害死一个人 居然连一点悔悟之心也没有
I'm doing justice.
我这是在为社会伸张正义
No, I mean Mr. Kim and Mr. Kang.
不 我是指金大叔他们
Why did you kill them?
为什么要杀他们？
Was it to silence them?
是为了灭口吗？
Then you could have made it quick.
那你大可以给他们一个痛快
Yet you avoided inflicting fatal wounds, as if to torture them.
然而你却刻意避开了致命伤
It's for the victim? Cut it out.
你说是为了被害人？少来了
That is not your true nature.
那才不是你的本质
Yes.
好的
These things are trivial for me.
那对我来说轻而易举
But you seem to have misunderstood.
但你似乎有所误解
I am a B-rank hunter that many large guilds fight for.
我可是许多大型公会 抢着要的B级猎人
Why do you think I joined Hunter's Association that pays a meager salary?
你觉得我这样的人 为什么会加入月薪微薄的猎人协会？
Because compared to killing magic beasts,
我啊
I enjoy killing people more.
杀人类更能让我感到开心
Even with a second awakening, an E-rank hunter can't be very strong.
E级猎人就算二次觉醒 也不会强到哪里去
You're too slow.
-太慢了 -确实有两把刷子
How can he have such skills?
他怎么会有这种身手？
He's no longer the Sung I knew.
他已经完全不是 我所认识的那个阿成了！
-Our speeds are comparable.
-速度不相上下
Even if we have the same skills
就算拥有相同的技术与相同的实力
your experience against high-level opponents
我们与高等对手的 实战经验次数差很多
You are a tough one.
很有毅力嘛
-Excuse me. -What?
不好意思
Could you please tone down your killing intent?
可以麻烦你收一下杀气吗？
Look.
你看
The system has responded to you.
系统对你起反应了
Now I have to thank this system.
我已经很久没有这么感谢这个系统了
It has given me another reason why I must kill you.
让我又多了一个非杀你不可的理由
System?
“系统”？
What's up with him?
这家伙是怎么回事？
I'm the one with the upper hand.
占上风的人明明是我
He got even faster.
又变得更快了
It's poison.
是毒
Is this a special effect of your dagger?
这是你那把短剑的特殊效果吗？
Then let me show you something interesting too.
那我也让你看个有趣的东西吧
He disappeared.
他消失了？
I had completely concealed my presence.
我明明已经将气息完全隐藏了
Your senses are sharp.
真是个敏锐的家伙
Skill, Invisibility.
技能隐身
It hides one's shape, sound, and scent, among others.
能隐藏身形、声音、气味等所有气息
Even among assassins, only a very few can acquire this skill.
就算在暗杀系猎人中 也只有极少数人能得到这个技能
Of course, those who know that I can use this skill
知道我能使用这个技能的人
are nonexistent.
一个都没有 毕竟啊…
there hasn't been one
从来没有任何人
who has seen me use this skill and lived to tell about it.
看过我使出这招后 还能活着回去
I have sealed your speed.
我封住了你的速度
-Jinwoo. -Stay put.
-振宇！ -别想乱来
After I kill him, it's your turn.
等我杀了他 再来就轮到你们了
If this goes on, Sung will…
这样下去的话 阿成会被…
With your foot injured, can you still dodge my attacks?
脚伤成那样 还有办法躲过我接下来的攻击吗？
Hey.
喂
Have you said enough?
你还要废话多久？
Full Recovery.
状态恢复
He recovered instantly.
居然在瞬间就恢复了
A fighter capable of using healing magic.
我从没听过有能使用 治疗魔法的战斗型猎人
How many times can he use it?
他还能再用几次？
I cannot predict it at all.
我完全无法预测
He's a dangerous one.
他是个危险人物
I've lost another emotion.
又有一种情绪消失了
With scum like you,
面对你这种人渣
it's a waste of time to get angry, I guess.
连生气都是浪费时间吗？
I see.
原来如此
You're like me after all.
什么嘛 原来是同路人啊
I see.
我懂了
He probably had to make many difficult choices in a short time.
他恐怕是在短时间里
It isn't just his appearance that changed.
他改变的不只是外表而已
Awakening.
觉醒
This power beyond common sense has changed the rules of the world.
这种超越常识的力量 改变了这个世界的规则
This is a lawless land belonging only to hunters.
这里是只属于猎人的法外之地
There is no law here.
在这里不需要遵守法律规定
The strong will win.
强者自然能够胜出
Can he be
这家伙…
gauging my position through my killing intent?
难道是通过我的杀气 来感应我在哪里？
But even so, he still can't pinpoint my exact location.
但即便加此 他还是无法掌握我的正确位置
What… what's happening?
怎么了？
Wait.
等一下
No way.
不会吧
How…
这是怎么回事？
You asked me why I killed, right?
你问过我为什么要杀人对吧？
It's pointless to apply ordinary people's views
将一般人认知的常识
to hunters who frequently consort with death.
套用在常与死亡为伍的猎人身上 是没有意义的
You're the same.
你也一样
We've both become killing machines.
我们都已经是杀人机器了
So, I lost and will die.
所以败阵的我将会死亡
It's the logical rule.
这是合理至极的法则
Who are you?
你到底是何方神圣？
Being an assassin, you're capable of using healing magic and debuff magic.
明明是暗杀系猎人
I've never heard of that.
我没听过有这种事
I would like to know too.
连我也很好奇自己身上出了什么事
Since you've killed me,
你既然杀了我
you can no longer hide your identity.
那也无法再继续隐藏身份了
What if I were the kind of hunter who grows constantly in battle?
如果说我是能在战斗中 不断成长的猎人的话呢？
Your shadow
你的影子啊
is already connected to the darkness.
已经跟黑暗相连了
Your power will become as unfathomable as it.
你的力量将会 变得跟它一样深不可测吧
However, you must be careful.
然而你要小心
When you stare into the abyss,
当你凝视着深渊时
the abyss stares back at you.
深渊也同时在凝视着你
Indeed.
我的实力的确已经不可同日而语
But I feel
但莫名地觉得…
that as my strength grows,
在实力变强的同时
a part of me is gradually falling apart.
体内的某个东西也正在逐渐崩坏
Jinwoo.
振宇
Thank you.
谢谢你
You saved us.
幸好有你救了我们
Without you, we would have died.
要是没有你 我们早就死了
It's nothing.
不客气
Please go ahead and leave.
请你们先出去吧
I need to close up the dungeon.
得让地下城关起来才行
What?
什么？你该不会想一个人去吧？
No, we'll do as you say.
不 还是照你说的做吧
It's a pity that we can't bury Kim and Kang.
虽然无法替老金他们安葬 让人感到遗憾
I'll wait for you outside.
我在外面等你
Chief Woo.
禹科长
I've heard the report. Where are the survivors?
报告我听说了
Over there.
在那边
Speaking of which,
话说回来
I didn't expect Kang Taeshik to be involved in murders.
想不到姜泰植 会在暗地里干着杀人的勾当
Although I did suspect him,
虽然早就觉得他有点可疑
as his superior, I was too careless.
只能说我这个上司太过大意了
It's these three.
就是这三位
I remember
我记得他是当时的那位E级猎人
He looks like a different person.
简直就是脱胎换骨
Long time no see.
好久不见
Um, you're from the Surveillance Team.
那个 你是监察科的人吧
Woo Jinchul.
我是禹镇澈
This time, my subordinate has caused huge trouble.
这次我们的职员 惹出了无法弥补的大麻烦
But first,
不过首先呢
let me get straight to the point.
我就单刀直入地问了
Which of you killed Kang Taeshik?
打败了姜泰植的人是哪一位？
It's a pity.
真可惜
My collaboration with Jinho might have to come to an end.
轸皓的提议可能无法实现了
It was me.
是我
I killed Mr. Kang.
姜先生是死在我的手上
Excuse me, I remember your rank is…
恕我失礼 我记得你的等级是…
I'm a C-rank hunter.
我是C级
How could a C-rank hunter manage to kill a B-rank hunter?
C级的你怎么会有办法杀掉B级的他？
Because we have her.
不是还有她在吗？
I see.
原来如此
So you managed to defeat him with the healer's assistance.
借助治疗师的辅助 才得以打败他啊
Kang Taeshik was among the top of the B-rank hunters.
姜泰植在B级猎人中 实力也位居前列
I don't think a C-rank mage could kill him, no matter how hard he tried.
一个C级的法师再怎么挣扎 我也不觉得能赢得过
I understand.
我明白了
We need to complete the report.
我们得去完成事件笔录
Please come with me.
请跟我走一趟吧
Now is not the time to be smug about having killed Kang Taeshik.
现在不是因为打倒姜泰植 而沾沾自喜的时候了
This person is an A-rank hunter.
这个人是A级猎人
He's not someone I can handle right now.
不是现在的我所能应付的对手
Was I meddling too much?
是我多管闲事了吗？
You must have your reasons for hiding your strength.
你之所以会隐藏实力 应该有你的苦衷吧
All right. Consider it my way of repaying you for saving my life.
不过就当作是我报答你的救命之恩吧
Three hours later,
三小时后
the man who commissioned Kang Taeshik to kill the prisoners turned himself in.
委托姜泰植杀死囚犯的男人去自首
The whole case was concluded as legitimate self-defense.
整个案子以我们是正当防卫结案
That was exhausting.
累死人了
Jinwoo.
振宇
Do you
这个…
remember this?
你还记得吗？